digitaslbi.com 2015-12-07

# Privacy Statement and Cookie Information - DigitasLBi

### Privacy statement

**Overview  
** Thank you for visiting the DigitasLBi Website (" **Website** "), owned and operated by DigitasLBi ("DigitasLBi," "we," "us," "our," or other similar pronouns). This privacy policy (" **Privacy Policy** ") governs your use of the Website. By accessing or using the Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as they may be amended from time to time. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and part of, the DigitasLBi[Terms of Use](http://www.digitas.com/terms.html), which governs your use of the Website in general.

Your privacy is a serious matter to us and we have created this Privacy Policy to inform you of how we collect, use, share, and secure your Personal Information. " **Personal Information** " includes your full name, address, e-mail address, other information that may identify you as an individual or allow online or offline contact with you, and any other non-personally identifiable information associated with Personal Information. This Privacy Policy explains, in general, what Personal Information and other information is collected on the Website, how the information is used, and with whom we may share such information. Please take a few minutes to read our Privacy Policy so that you understand how DigitasLBi treats your Personal Information. It is our general policy not to share your Personal Information with third parties for such third parties' direct marketing purposes without your consent.

**Applicability of this Privacy Policy  
** This Privacy Policy applies to both information we may collect online and information we may collect through the Website, but does not apply to information collected through other sources or from third parties.

**Notice**

**Information Digitas LBi collects  
**DigitasLBi may collect information in a number of ways in connection with the Website, including, without limitation, as follows:

  * When clients access their DigitasLBi Team Site.
  * When you create an account at our "Careers" section.
  * When you submit a resume or other information to be considered for employment with DigitasLBi
  * When you ask us a question, we collect the e-mail address or other contact information you choose to provide.
  * When you request an e-mail be sent to a friend through the Website, we will collect your and your friend's e-mail addresses.
  * When you voluntarily provide Personal Information to us for any other purpose.

**How Digitas LBi uses your information**

  * To generally provide the features and functionality of the Website to you.
  * For account validation purposes.
  * To consider your candidacy for employment.
  * For analytics and trending purposes.
  * To identify you as the sender of, and to process, your forwarded e-mails.
  * To respond to questions and comments.
  * To improve, enhance, and tailor the Website for you, and to improve and enhance the overall Website experience for all the Website users.
  * To carry out specific actions you may request.

**To whom Digitas LBi discloses your information  
**DigitasLBi may disclose to third parties Personal Information that it collects as follows:

  * **Operation of the Website:  **We disclose your Personal Information to third parties where necessary to provide the Website and its features and functionality to you.
  * **At Your Request:**  We disclose your Personal Information to a third party whenever you request us to do so.
  * **Business transfers:**  If a third party acquires all or substantially all of DigitasLBi' assets, your Personal Information, aggregated information, and any other information that we have collected in connection with the Website may be transferred to such third party as part of our business assets. Also, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, all such information may be considered one of our assets and may be sold or transferred to third parties.
  * **Disclosure of Personal Information for legal purposes and protection of Digitas LBi and others:** We reserve the right to share your Personal Information with third parties if required to do so by law, or if we believe such action is necessary in order to: (1) conform to the requirements of the law or comply with legal process served upon us; (2) protect or defend our legal rights or property, the Website, or our users; or (3) investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or violations of the DigitasLBi Terms of Use.
  * **Service Providers:  **We use third-party service providers, including but not limited to our affiliates, to perform certain services on our behalf, such as processing, storing, maintaining and transmitting data, processing and fulfilling e-mail and other promotional campaigns, and providing marketing assistance, web analytics, and data analysis. We may provide your Personal Information to these third-party service providers when the information is necessary for them to perform their duties. These third-party service providers are contractually restricted from using Personal Information for any other purpose and required to comply with all applicable laws with respect to the Personal Information they receive.
  * **Government Agencies:**  We will disclose your Personal Information to third parties if required to do so by law.
  * **As Otherwise Permitted By Law.**  We may disclose your Personal Information to third parties as otherwise permitted by applicable law.

**Automatically collected non-Personal Information  
** When you use the Website, we also may collect certain standard information from your browser and personal computer that websites often collect, such as your IP address, your browser information (including browser type, capabilities, and language), your operating system, and the date and time you accessed the Website. We also capture the country from which the visit came and the paths taken as you move from one website or webpage to another website or webpage (i.e., your "click stream" activity). We may group some or all of this information into aggregate data in order to describe the use of the Website by our users to our existing or potential business partners, sponsors, advertisers, or other third parties, or in response to a government request. We may also group demographic information that we collect from the Website users into aggregate data for the same purposes. We reserve the right to use and share any such non-Personal Information collected at the Website with third parties for any lawful purpose.

DigitasLBi does not typically associate such non-Personal Information with any individual. However, to the extent DigitasLBi associates your Personal Information with non-Personal Information within our database, we will treat all the associated information as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy. Except as noted in this Privacy Policy, we do not share this associated information with third parties.

**Browsing and the use of cookies, Web beacons, and other tracking technologies  
** DigitasLBi uses cookie technology as part of the Website's statistical reporting and for other purposes related to making the Website available to you. A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a website that is saved on your hard disk by your computer's browser. It holds information a website may need to personalize your experience. We may also utilize cookies to identify if you are logged into a Website account.

If you prefer, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies, or to notify you when a cookie is set. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie and privacy preferences. However, if you reject cookies, your use of the Website may be impaired.

A Web beacon is an electronic image, also called a single-pixel or clear GIF, placed in the code of a webpage or in e-mails. The Website uses Web beacons to track traffic patterns of users as they navigate from one page to another. This information lets us tune and improve our users' browsing experience. As with cookies, the information that Web beacons collect is aggregated, anonymous "click stream" data, and is not associated with you as an individual.

We also use Web beacons through a third party Website analytics provider, as well as standard Web server log files, to help us count visitors and evaluate the Website's technical capacity. This information tells us how many people visit the Website, and helps us decide how to arrange pages in the most user-friendly way. This also helps us keep the Website browser-friendly and more useful to our users. We record information on Website traffic, but not on individual visitors to the Website, so no Personal Information about you will be kept or used.

**Careers  
** If you submit your resume or other information to be considered for employment with DigitasLBi and you choose to send your resume or other information to us through this Website or the Internet, we will maintain and use the information provided only for such purpose. If you choose to establish an account with our career center, the information you submit may be retained in accordance with the "Access and Data Retention" section below.

**Information posted to any forums, chats, or blogs  
** If you choose to use a forum, a blog, participate in a chat room, or otherwise use a social networking feature available through the Website, you should be aware that any Personal Information or other information you post can be read, collected, or used by other users of the Website, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages or used in an otherwise unauthorized manner. We cannot be responsible for any Personal Information you choose to post through those means and we recommend careful consideration before you post such information.

**E-mail to a friend  
** You may be able to send particular information about the Website to your friends and family members through the Website by clicking on an "E-mail to Friend" or similar button on the Website. In some cases (unless you simply forward our e-mail on your own), you may provide the name and email address of your friend or family member to us. Such information will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable law.

**Third party websites, content, and resources  
** Please be aware that when you are using the Website, you could be directed via links or other means to third party websites, content, and resources that are not affiliated with the Website. These third party websites, content, and resources may send their own cookies to visitors, collect data, or solicit and use your Personal Information in ways different than set forth in this Privacy Policy. The privacy policies of these third party websites, content, and resources may be very different from this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of the providers of these other websites, content, and resources and cannot guarantee the security of any of your Personal Information collected, used, or shared there.

**Our policy regarding selling or renting of Personal Information  
** It is our policy not to sell or rent your Personal Information to any third party, except in the event of a bankruptcy or reorganization, or a sale of all or substantially all of our assets, as further provided in this Privacy Policy.

**Consent to processing (for users within the European Union)  
** By providing Personal Information to this Website, you understand and consent to the collection, maintenance, processing, and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other countries and territories, outside the European Economic Area (" **EEA** "), which may not have data protection laws as comprehensive as those that exist in the EEA.

**A special note about minors  
** The Website is intended for use only by persons who are at least 18 years of age and who are fully able and competent to enter into and be legally bound by this Privacy Policy. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone whom we know to be under 13 years of age.

**Access And Data Retention**

**How to update, correct, or delete certain of your Personal Information  
** You can access and modify certain Personal Information stored at the Website, if you have submitted Personal Information through our careers page, such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, and telephone number, by logging into your account at the Website.

You may also delete your account. Deletion of your account will only result in deletion of your online account and will not affect Personal Information that may have been previously sent by us pursuant to your request, as in the case where you submit a resume. Upon deletion of your account, DigitasLBi will delete your account from our primary Website servers. Notwithstanding the foregoing, DigitasLBi will retain certain information (including Personal Information) provided to us for the following or other lawful purposes:

  * Auditing purposes
  * Troubleshoot problems
  * Assist with investigations
  * Enforce the DigitasLBi Terms of Use
  * Comply with legal requirements

Therefore, you should not expect that all of your Personal Information will always be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests. In addition, please note that after your Personal Information is removed, there may be residual information that remains within one of our databases that may or may not contain your Personal Information, such as information that may be retained in back-up servers. DigitasLBi will apply this Privacy Policy to information we maintain regarding former users of the Website.

**Security**

**How we protect the security of your Personal Information  
** DigitasLBi will take reasonable steps to protect the security and integrity of all Personal Information provided to this Website. However, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers. We will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties during or after transmission.

You are responsible for maintaining the strict confidentiality of your account password, and you shall be responsible for any access to or use of the Website by you or any person or entity using your password, whether or not such access or use has been authorized by or on behalf of you, and whether or not such person or entity is your employee or agent. You agree to immediately notify DigitasLBi of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security.

In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your Personal Information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, and, to the extent we have your e-mail address, we may notify you by e-mail. You consent to our use of e-mail as a means of such notification.

**Privacy Policy Updates  
** This Privacy Policy was updated on the "Effective Date" noted below. DigitasLBi reserves the right to change, modify, or amend this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes in our privacy practices. You are encouraged to review this Privacy Policy periodically and to check the "Effective Date" at the bottom of this Privacy Policy for the most recent version to inform yourself about how your Personal Information is collected, used, and shared when you use the Website. To the fullest extent under applicable law, your use of the Website after the "Effective Date" means you are subject to the Privacy Policy then in effect.

**Contact Us  
** How to contact DigitasLBi regarding your privacy concerns and questions

If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy practices, you may contact us at [law@DigitasLBi.com](mailto:law@digitas.com).

**Effective Date: 17 June, 2013**
